[Music]
[音乐]
此卡是一张生日贺卡，其中包含
this card is a birthday card containing
一条船，在这种情况下，我已经完成了
猫头鹰和猫咪非常简单
this card is a birthday card containing
a boat and in this case I've done the
机制，它基于教程14
这是盒子的一个例子
a boat and in this case I've done the
Owl and the Pussycat it's quite a simple
您可以看到它是两个
平行四边形背对背，这是
Owl and the Pussycat it's quite a simple
mechanism it's based on tutorial 14
最终使它成为一个
刚性形状，而不是这种情况
mechanism it's based on tutorial 14
which is the box is an example of the
它只是一块扁平的东西
在盒子的末端，我们得到了
which is the box is an example of the
box as you can see it's two
船形这横跨
盒子，把整个东西都固定住了
box as you can see it's two
parallelograms back-to-back and it's the
这些所需的零件
是我已经切掉的部分
parallelograms back-to-back and it's the
piece on the end that makes it into a
并测量他们这是两个位
这将变成平行四边形
piece on the end that makes it into a
rigid shape and in this case rather than
这是三个部分2,5厘米2,5
2,5两端各带有一个标签
rigid shape and in this case rather than
it being just a flat piece that goes
他们只有5厘米宽，
然后这些是船的侧面
it being just a flat piece that goes
across the end of the box we've got the
从折痕到折痕都是16
厘米，您在屏幕上有两个标签
across the end of the box we've got the
boat shape this goes across the end of
一块的另一端
件不需要标签，所以从
boat shape this goes across the end of
the box and holds the whole thing rigid
山寨到山寨那16
厘米，最后一块是
the box and holds the whole thing rigid
the parts you need to make this these
桅杆，所以现在我将向您展示
首先把它们粘在一起
the parts you need to make this these
are the parts I've already cut them out
确保所有折痕都是真的
执行得好，所以我将所有折痕
are the parts I've already cut them out
and measured them these are the two bits
那些
当您制作这些时，您不需要
and measured them these are the two bits
which will turn into the parallelograms
测量碎片在哪里
基地，所以我就开始一个你
which will turn into the parallelograms
it's three sections 2,5 centimeters 2,5
将其中一个标签粘在与
脊柱确保胶水正确向上
it's three sections 2,5 centimeters 2,5
2,5 with a tab at each end and both of
折痕，然后将其粘贴在
中间与脊柱齐平，然后
2,5 with a tab at each end and both of
them they're just 5 centimetres wide and
找到它折叠起来的自然粘住的地方
整个事情都变成了什么
them they're just 5 centimetres wide and
then these are the sides of the boat
处于关闭位置
将胶水放在另一个标签上，然后折叠
then these are the sides of the boat
from crease to crease it's 16
底座关闭，这样您就可以
第一个平行四边形再下一个
from crease to crease it's 16
centimetres you've got two tabs on the
您将其一侧与
脊柱
centimetres you've got two tabs on the
end of one of the pieces and the other
将其折叠到关闭位置并放入
粘在另一个标签上，然后折叠
end of one of the pieces and the other
piece doesn't need tabs so from the
基地关闭了，所以这是你的两个
平行四边形现在是您的机会
piece doesn't need tabs so from the
cottage to the cottage that 16
一分钟后，我们就在桅杆上
将他们背靠背制作
cottage to the cottage that 16
centimetres and the final piece this is
实心形状，但在执行此操作之前
你可以把桅杆或帆或
centimetres and the final piece this is
the mast so now I'll just show you how
其他任何事情，所以你只需要放一点
粘在那根棍子上，现在
the mast so now I'll just show you how
to stick them all together first of all
你把胶水全部涂在其中之一上
表面将其关闭，所以就在
to stick them all together first of all
make sure all the creases are really
两个平行四边形仍然不是
稳定的形状，因为没有任何东西
make sure all the creases are really
well enforced so I'll just crease all
连接这两个外侧，所以我会
只需将两个船片粘合在一起
well enforced so I'll just crease all
those
这样它们可以同时粘在一起
时间
when you're making these you don't need
因此您可以在
现在隐藏在你里面
when you're making these you don't need
to measure where the pieces go on the
下来在这里坚持那些
两侧使整个事情变得僵化
to measure where the pieces go on the
base so I'll just start with one you
所以我们再次将胶水涂在这些
外边缘将其放置到位，您
base so I'll just start with one you
glue one of the tabs flush with the
可以真正将其居中
盒子是否真的无关紧要
glue one of the tabs flush with the
spine make sure the glue goes right up
形状实际上是书写还是不书写
卡在外面的边缘上就可以看到
spine make sure the glue goes right up
to the crease and you stick that in the
当它关闭船的尽头
实际上抬起，但这是一个
to the crease and you stick that in the
middle flush with the spine and then to
盒机构14和
这是您可以开始的地方
middle flush with the spine and then to
find its natural sticking place you fold
添加装饰品，在这种情况下
猫头鹰被困在
find its natural sticking place you fold
the whole thing into its what's going to
小船猫咪卡在桅杆
您可以根据需要添加标志
the whole thing into its what's going to
be its closed position
也有沟渠在这里你可以建立
到这里，您可以建立另一个
be its closed position
put glue on that other tab and then fold
从教程8讲到有关添加
您可以添加的3d小片段
put glue on that other tab and then fold
the base closed so that gives you your
这些沟渠中的任何一个
卡关闭，所以这是你的船
the base closed so that gives you your
first parallelogram the next one again
确实想在其中建一个甲板
实际上必须将其调整为
first parallelogram the next one again
you stick it one side flush with the
适合，所以如果我拿这张卡
在这里，您需要折痕
you stick it one side flush with the
spine
中间
你必须在中间有一个洞
fold it into its closed position and put
大师们要经历的
您需要它的长度与
fold it into its closed position and put
glue on the other tab and then you fold
整个船，所以这是一个结局
一端和另一端，所以这是要
glue on the other tab and then you fold
the base closed so these are your two
像那样贴在上面
向下到这个盒子形状的顶部，但是
the base closed so these are your two
parallelograms now is your chance to
使其真正适合
您只需要塑造它的形状
parallelograms now is your chance to
stick in the mast in a minute we're
量身定做，所以我就拿这个
并大致看一下我的形状
stick in the mast in a minute we're
going to stick them back to back to make
上船
这不适合在那里你可以看到
going to stick them back to back to make
the solid shape but before you do that
还是有点大，我差不多
那里我要多花点时间
the solid shape but before you do that
you can put in the mast or sail or
就在那边，所以现在适合
上船我可以把它再次放出来
you can put in the mast or sail or
anything else so you just put a bit of
盒子顶部的胶水
涂抹在周围，确保折痕是
anything else so you just put a bit of
glue on that stick that in place and now
好，所以甲板会保持平整
当船开的时候
glue on that stick that in place and now
you put glue all over one of these
只要把它放在你按下的嘴上
它下降到那些在那里，所以现在
you put glue all over one of these
surfaces close it so there it is it's
您将其关闭，甲板随即关闭
船，所以你真的不需要甲板
surfaces close it so there it is it's
the two parallelograms it's still not a
如果你看这个没有甲板
作为设计，它确实可以很好地工作
the two parallelograms it's still not a
stable shape because there's nothing
令人满意，那就是船
生日贺卡由您决定
stable shape because there's nothing
joining these two outer sides so I'll
用其他任何装饰
您喜欢使用的作品
joining these two outer sides so I'll
just glue the two boat pieces together
有关人员的照片或
剪下碎片和其他明信片或
so these can be glued both at the same
任何有趣的鱼美人鱼船长
哈巴狗给你
so these can be glued both at the same
time
您
[音乐]
so you keep any measuring marks on the